Hi.
So in this clip we're going to take our bound button hole and we're going to be pressing on the wrong side as well as pinning it.
So once you turn it inside out it looks like this.
And now what we're going to do is press it.
Go ahead and take your iron and you just want to press it kind of flat.
Get out any crinkles.
So now what you're going to be doing is pushing the fabric inward a little bit so that both the top and the bottom are even.
So turn it to the wrong side and just fold up the fabric just a little.
And you want to take some pins and go ahead and pin it in please.
And you kind of have to play with this a little bit to get it perfect.
So, you kind of push down the fabric on the top, pin that in place and then come around to the front and look at how it looks.
And this will determine how much more you need to push it in to place.
And the whole point is you want to line up the fabric so that they both meet in the center but that they're equal distances apart.
So in this case the bottom's a little bit too far out.
So we're going to take it in a little bit.